# Syed Jafor Hussain

## Mobile Application Developer

Accomplished Mobile Application Developer who is able to create mobile applications for every mobile software operating system platform. Adept at developing apps based on customer specification recommending application changes to make more efficient programs and upgrading existing apps to make them more useful. Specializes in corporate and industrial applications.



sjhnadeem@gmail.com 🔀

01685792139

Dhaka, Bangladesh 👂

sjhnadeem.github.io/

linkedin.com/in/syedjafor in

twitter.com/syedjafor

github.com/sjhnadeem 🔘

stackoverflow.com/users/12273383/syed- hussain

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Developer Workplace/Company

01/2020 - Present

**Mentor**Workplace/Company

01/2017 - Present

**Co-Founder** WeaverMesh

01/2017 - 12/2019

Monitoring Officer
DHL

05/2014 - 12/2014

#### **EDUCATION**

**B.Sc in Computer Science & Engineering** Stamford University Bangladesh

01/2014 - 01/2018

HSC

Longla Adunik Degree College

01/2010 - 01/2012

## **SKILLS**



## PERSONAL PROJECTS

Mobile Application (01/2017 - 01/2018)

 In-depth understanding of computer programming language and ability to code. Knowledge of most types of graphic design software and application.

#### Graphic Designer (01/2018 - 12/2019)

- By using the latest Operating Systems and tools my career as a Graphic Designer,I have been able to achieve a level of recognition as an expert in my field.
- Responsible for Graphic Design & Branding, Logo Design, Social Media promotion, Presentations, and Support.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Android Developer (01/2018)

Mobile Application ICT IT training for Android Mobile Application.

#### LANGUAGES

English Bangla
Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### INTERESTS

